Finding Aid for the Anne Waldman Papers, 1945-2012
Anne Waldman Papers
- Correspondence and Name File
  - Name File
    - Ginsberg, Allen
      - Manuscripts
        - Letters to Yugoslavia (Vojo Sindolic) from "Beat Scene", 1981-1992 (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous poetry manuscripts, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous prose manuscripts, 1969-1985 undated (Box 9)
      - Printed material
        - Poetry and broadsides, 1977-1977 (Box 9)
        - Clippings (2 folders), 1979-1994 (Box 10)
        - Programs and invitations, 1979-2005 (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Biographical summary, ca. 1978 (Box 10)
        - Ginsberg Trust, 1994-1998 (Box 10)
        - Interviews,(audio cassette in audiovisual series) 1976-1996 (Box 10)
        - Interview with Vojo Sindolic, 1986 (Box 10)
        - Memorials and obituaries (2 folders), 1997 (Box 10)
        - Anne Waldman's speech for tree planting memorial at St. Mark's Church-in-the-Bowery August 18, 1999 (Box 10)
        - Rhino compact disc boxed set ( Allen Ginsberg: A Recorded History) correspondence and liner notes by Anne Waldman, 1993 (Box 10)
        - Teaching material, 1983 (Box 10)
        - Travel itineraries, 1979-1996 (Box 10)
        - Anne Waldman "notes on a conversation with Allen G," 1994 (Box 10)
        - Various, undated (Box 10)
        - Allen Ginsberg's necktie (red and blue stripe) (Box 10)
      - Notes
        - Door notes and messages for Anne Waldman, undated (Box 10)
        - "Rinpoche lectures": photocopies (2 folders), 1973 (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous notes and jottings, undated (Box 10)
    - Giorno, John
      - Correspondence, 1970-1986, undated (Box 10)
      - Manuscripts, 1973-1974, undated (Box 10)
      - Flyers, posters, and announcements, 1968-1971, undated (Box 10)
      - Giorno Poetry Systems
        - Contracts with Anne Waldman, 1978-1980 (Box 10)
        - Press Releases, 1970, undated (Box 10)
    - Glasser, Jane Ellen, 1973, undated (Box 10)
    - Glassgold, Peter (New Directions Publishing), 1976-1991 (Box 10)
    - Glenn, Tamela, undated (Box 10)
    - Godfrey, John, 1980, undated (Box 10)
    - Goheen, Ellen R., 1980 (Box 10)
    - Goldberg, Jeff, undated (Box 10)
    - Goldberg, Natalie
      - Correspondence, 1986-1994, undated (Box 10)
      - Manuscript, Long Quiet Highway, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Golde, Morris, 1973-1980 (Box 10)
    - Goldfarb, Sidney, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Goldstein, Richard, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Goodell, Larry, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Goodfriend, Gloria, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Gordon, Kirpal Singh, undated (Box 10)
    - Granville-Smith, Maureen, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Graverholz, James W. 1999 (Box 10)
    - Gray, Darrell, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Gray, Francine, 1974 (Box 10)
    - Gray, Paul, 1975 (Box 10)
    - Green, Galen, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Greenspan, Eliot, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Greenwald, Ted
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976, undated (Box 10)
      - Manuscript, "Native Land," 1976 (Box 10)
    - Griffin, Tom, undated (Box 10)
    - Grimm, David (6 folders), 1963-1976, undated (Box 11)
    - Groffsky, Maxine ( The Paris Review), 1973, undated (Box 11)
    - Grooms, Red, 1984, undated (Box 11)
    - Grossinger, Richard, 1984, undated (Box 11)
    - Gruntz, George, 1972-2004 (Box 11)
    - Guarino, Mariangela (City Lights Italia), 1998-2002 (Box 11)
    - Guest, Barbara, 1973-2002, undated (Box 11)
    - Gunreben, Ulrich, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Guravich, Donald, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Gustafson, Jim, 1979, undated (Box 11)
    - Guston, Philip, 1971-1977 (Box 11)
    - Hacker, Marilyn, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Haden-Guest, Hadley, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Haerdter, Micheal, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Haines, Randa, 1964-1968 (Box 11)
    - Hall, Donald, 1971-1994, undated (Box 11)
    - Hall, James Baker, 1977, undated (Box 11)
    - Hall, Steven (2 folders), 1976-1979, undated (Box 11)
    - Hall, Susan, 1973-1989 (Box 11)
    - Hallett, Marta (Stonehill Publishing), 1975-1980, undated (Box 11)
    - Hamill, Juan, undated (Box 11)
    - Hamilton, Steve, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Hamlin, Louise, 1994,2001 (Box 11)
    - Hammersley, Richard, undated (Box 11)
    - Hampson, Robert, 1977, 2006 (Box 11)
    - Hansen, Al, 1966 (Box 11)
    - Haring, Cynthia, 1977-1979 (Box 11)
    - Harryman, Carla, 1993-1997 (Box 11)
    - Hartman, Yukihede Maeshima, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Hartz, Jim, undated (Box 11)
    - Harwood, Lee, 1970-1991 (Box 11)
    - Havelin, Jim, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
    - Haviaras, Stratis, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
    - Hawkins, Bobbie Louise
      - Correspondence, 1973-2006 (Box 11)
      - Manuscripts, 1993, undated (Box 11)
    - Hawkins, Ralph, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Haynes, Douglas, 1978, undated (Box 11)
    - Hejinian, Lyn, 1976-1993, 200, 2003, undated (Box 11)
    - Heliczer, Piero, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Heller, Michael, 1980-1991 (Box 11)
    - Hemenway, Anne, 2000-2002 (Box 11)
    - Henderson, David, 1970-1993 (Box 11)
    - Hershon, Bob, 1990-1993 (Box 11)
    - Hertz, Amy (Henry Holt and Company), 1991 (Box 11)
    - Hickox, Fayette, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Higgins, Dick, 1969-1973 (Box 11)
    - Hiler, Jerry, 1971-1992, 1999 (Box 11)
    - Hillinghouse, Mark, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Hinchey, John, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    - Hine, Daryl (Poetry Magazine), 1973 (Box 11)
    - Hintze, Christian Ide (Schule für Dichtung), 1991-1999, undated (Box 11)
    - Hobson, Gerald, undated (Box 11)
    - Hodgekiss, Peter, (Galloping Dog Press), 1978 (Box 11)
    - Hoffman, Andy, 1986-2007, undated (Box 11)
    - Holland, Joyce, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Hollo, Anselm
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1972-2006, undated (Box 12)
      - Manuscripts, 1998, undated (Box 12)
      - Printed Material, 1979-1991 (Box 12)
      - Biographical, undated (Box 12)
    - Hollowell, Amy, 1999-2000 (Box 12)
    - Holman, Bob, 1979-1992, 1996, 2000-2006 (Box 12)
    - Hoogstraten, Harry and Suze, 1979-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Hoover, Paul ( Oink and Columbia Poetry Review ), 1984-2002 (Box 12)
    - Hopper, Jack, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Horne, Jed ( People Magazine), 1975 (Box 12)
    - Hornick, Lita
      - Correspondence, 1973-1984, undated (Box 12)
      - Manuscripts and announcements, 1991, undated (Box 12)
    - Horowitz, Michael, 1969-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Hough, Lindy, 1975, 2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Hourwich, Sasha, 1958-1967, undated (Box 12)
    - Howe, Susan, undated (Box 12)
    - Howard, Snooks, undated (Box 12)
    - Hoyem, Andrew, 1970-1978 (Box 12)
    - Hrdy, Becky, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Hrebeniak, Michael, undated (Box 12)
    - Hudson, Lee (University of Texas Austin), 1979 (Box 12)
    - Hudspith, Vicki, 1984, 2001, undated (Box 12)
    - Hughes, Helena, 1978-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Humann, Klaus, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Hunt, Laird, 1995-2004 (Box 12)
    - Hunter, Robert, 1992-1993 (Box 12)
    - Hurwitz, Sidney, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Hussey-Freke, Ambrose, 1980-1981 (Box 12)
    - Irby, Kenneth, 1989-1993, 2000-2002 (Box 12)
    - Jackson, Haziel, undated (Box 12)
    - Jackson, Richard, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Jacob, John, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Jacquette, Yvonne, 1987-1989, undated (Box 12)
    - Janovy, Jennifer, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Jarnot, Lisa, 1996-2007 (Box 12)
    - Jenkins, Joyce ( Poetry Flash), 1978-1995, undated (Box 12)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1972-1984, undated (Box 12)
    - Johnson, Kent, 1988-1991 (Box 12)
    - Johnston, Alastair, 1977-1998 (Box 12)
    - Jordan, Dawn, undated (Box 12)
    - Joris, Pierre, 1973-1974, 2000, undated (Box 12)
    - Josek, Jiri, 1993-2002 (Box 12)
    - Kahn, Paul, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Kaiser, Thomas, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Kaminker, Karin, 1993-2002 (Box 12)
    - Kamsler, Mark, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Kass, Ray, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Katz, Alex and Ada, 1968-1980, undated (Box 12)
    - Katz, Eliot, 1981-2007 (Box 12)
    - Katz, Leandro, 1994, 2002, undated (Box 12)
    - Katz, Steve, 1985, undated (Box 12)
    - Katz, Vincent, 1986-2004 (Box 12)
    - Kearney, Margaret
      (also known as Tapa Kearney)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979, undated (Box 12)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 12)
    - Kellner, Michael, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Kelly, Robert, 1977 (Box 12)
    - Kensho, Hugo, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Kerouac, Jan, undated (Box 12)
    - Kerouac, Jack, 1962 (Box 12)
    - Kesey, Ken
      - Correspondence, 1975-1999 (Box 12)
      - Lecture transcript and photograph, 1975 (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976, undated (Box 12)
      - Knott, Beverly (Follett Publishing Company), 1968 (Box 12)
    - Kicknosway, Faye (also known as Morgan Blair), 1974 (Box 12)
    - Kimball, George, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Kimberly, Nick, 1970-1974 (Box 12)
    - King, Basil, undated (Box 12)
    - King, Denyse, 1980 (Box 12)
    - King, Kenneth, 1973-1976 (Box 12)
    - Kinnel, Galway, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Kirschenbaum, David, 1993, 2007 (Box 12)
    - Kissam, Ed, undated (Box 12)
    - Kite, Mary, 2001-2004 (Box 12)
    - Knight, Arthur and Glee, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Knipscheer, Jos, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Knowles, Christopher, undated (Box 13)
    - Koch, Kenneth
      - Correspondence, 1969-1994 (Box 13)
      - Printed material, undated (Box 13)
      - Biographical, 1977, undated (Box 13)
    - Koethe, Jolen, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Kohler, Michael, 1972-1988, undated (Box 13)
    - Koller, Jim, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Kong, Gail (Coordinating Council of Literary Magazines), 1972-1973 (Box 13)
    - Kornblum, Allan
      - Correspondence, 1979-1995, 2000-2006, undated (Box 13)
      - Coffee House Press, royalty statements, contracts, and miscellaneous, 1984-1996, 2001, undated (Box 13)
    - Kostakis, Peter ( Milk Quarterly and Yellow Press), 1975 (Box 13)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1973-1976 (Box 13)
    - Kramer, Robert, undated (Box 13)
    - Krauss, Ruth, 1969, undated (Box 13)
    - Kraut, Shelley, 1976-1981 (Box 13)
    - Kray, Elizabeth (Academy of American Poets), 1970 (Box 13)
    - Krieger, Ian, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Kumar, Radha, 1974, undated (Box 13)
    - Kurtz, Vivian, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13)
    - Kush (?) (Cloudhouse Poetry Archives), 1986-1998 (Box 13)
    - Kyger, Joanne
      - Correspondence (4 folders), 1971-2004, undated (Box 13)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 13)
      - Printed Material, 1973, undated (Box 13)
      - Interview: photocopy, 1983 (Box 13)
      - Artwork and miscellaneous, undated (Box 13)
    - Lacy, Steve, 1984-1998, 2001, undated (Box 13)
    - Lake, Eva, 1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Lally, Michael, 1973-1979, undated (Box 13)
    - Landes-Levi, Louise, 1991-1997 (Box 13)
    - Landry, John, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Langdell, Cheri Davis, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Larkin, Joan, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Larsen, Wenche, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Laughlin, James
      - Correspondence, 1976-1997 (Box 13)
      - Printed Material, 1986-1995 (Box 13)
      - Memorials and obituaries, 1997 (Box 13)
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 1981-1983, 2006, undated (Box 13)
    - Lawrance, Scott, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Lazzeri, Simone, 1979-1981 (Box 13)
    - Lea, Sonya, 2000-2002 (Box 13)
    - Lea, Sydney, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Lehnert, Richard, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Lemaine, Gerard-Georges, 1979-1983 (Box 13)
    - Lenhart, Gary, 1980-1989 (Box 13)
    - Lerner, Eric, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Lesniak, Rose
      - Correspondence, 1975-1989, undated (Box 13)
      - Manuscripts, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
      - Out There Productions video projects, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - LeSueur, Joe
      - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 13)
      - Manuscript, Four Apartments: an Intimate Memoir of Life with Frank O'Hara, 1991 (Box 13)
      - Interview, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Levendosky, Charlie, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
    - Levertov, Denise, 1994, undated (Box 13)
    - Levine, Les, 1973-1977 (Box 13)
    - Levine, Naomi, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Harry, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Joel, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Leyland, Winston ( Gay Sunshine), 1974 (Box 13)
    - Lichtenstein, Grace, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Liebhart, Ernst, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Lifshin, Lyn, 1976-1987, undated (Box 13)
    - Lloyd, Allan, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Loidl, Chris, 1990-2001 (Box 13)
    - London, Sara, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Loomis, Ed, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Lopate, Carol, undated (Box 13)
    - Low, Steven, 1976-1988, undated (Box 13)
    - Lustig, Shelley, 1982-1992 (Box 13)
    - Lynn, Lynn, 1979-1980, undated (Box 13)
    - MacAdams, Lewis
      - Correspondence, 1969-1999, undated (Box 14)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 14)
    - McAdams, Phoebe, 1972-1980 (Box 14)
    - MacArthur, Mary (Creative Artist Public Service Program), 1976-1977 (Box 14)
    - MacBeth, George, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Machovic, Martin, 1990, 1999 (Box 14)
    - MacInnis, Jamie, 1979 (Box 14)
    - MacKay, Bill, 1973, undated (Box 14)
    - Mac Low, Jackson
      - Correspondence, 1975-1994 (Box 14)
      - Manuscripts, 1980-1994 (Box 14)
    - MacNaughton, Ann, 1992, 1999 (Box 14)
    - Major, Clarence, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Malanga, Gerard
      - Correspondence, 1965-1991 (Box 14)
      - Printed Material, 1968-1970, undated (Box 14)
    - Malmude, Steve, 1974-1978 (Box 14)
    - Maluff, Saul, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Mapplethorpe, Robert, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Margolis, Susan, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - Marlatt, Daphne, 1978-1982 (Box 14)
    - Marron, John, 1973, undated (Box 14)
    - Martin, John (Black Sparrow Press), 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - Masters, Barbara, 1987-1997, undated (Box 14)
    - Masters, Greg, 1979-1992, undated (Box 14)
    - Masterson, Robert, 1990-1997 (Box 14)
    - Matthews, Harry, 1969-1974 (Box 14)
    - Matthias, John, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Mayer, Bernadette
      - Correspondence (4 folders), 1969-2002, undated (Box 14)
      - Manuscripts
        - Poetry, undated (Box 14)
        - Prose, undated (Box 14)
      - Printed, undated (Box 14)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 14)
    - Mayer, Musa, 1994 (Box 14)
    - McCall, Anthony, 1974 (Box 14)
    - McClure, Michael
      - Correspondence, 1973-2007, undated (Box 14)
      - Manuscripts, 1976-1992 (Box 14)
      - Printed material, 1972-1991, undated (Box 14)
    - McCrary, Jim
      - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
      - Manuscripts, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - McCullough, Frances, 1976 (Box 14)
    - McGrath, Thomas, 1974 (Box 14)
    - McKenna, Thomas, undated (Box 14)
    - McNaughton, Duncan, 1969-1987 (Box 14)
    - Meltzer, Richard, 1971-1988 (Box 14)
    - Merwin, W.S., 1975 (Box 14)
    - Messerli, Doug (Sun and Moon Press)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1997 (Box 14)
      - Manuscript, The Adventures Of, undated (Box 14)
    - Mikolowski, Ann and Ken, 1972-1995, 2002 (Box 14)
    - Miles, Alex, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Miles, Barry, 1974, undated (Box 14)
    - Miller, Stephen Paul (The Poetry Newsletter), undated (Box 14)
    - Minukin, Marta, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Mitchell, Donald, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Mitchell, Greg ( Crawdaddy magazine), 1974 (Box 14)
    - Mitgang, Esther (Stonehill Publishing and Harmony Books), 1977-1985 (Box 14)
    - Mohrenn, Wolfgang, undated (Box 14)
    - Montag, Tom, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Moon, Susan, 1997 (Box 14)
    - Moore, Honor, 1973-2009 (Box 14)
    - Morgan, Bill, 1994-2007 (Box 14)
    - Morgan, John and Linda, 1984-2001, undated (Box 14)
    - Morice, David, 1980-1994, undated (Box 14)
    - Morrisey, Stephen, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Morrison, Madison, 1973-1974, undated (Box 15)
    - Morrow, Bradford, 1982-1993 (Box 15)
    - Moscrip, Amos, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Mottram, Eric, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
    - Mukpo, Sawang Osel Rangdrol(?), 1992 (Box 15)
    - Mulford, Wendy, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Mulligan, John, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Mullins, Brighde (DIA Center for the Arts), 1994 (Box 15)
    - Mundhenk, Michael, 1980 (Box 15)
    - Munger, Nicky, 1963-1975, undated (Box 15)
    - Murray, Catherine, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1979-1989 (Box 15)
    - Nash, Susan, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Nations, Opal, 1971-1977, undated (Box 15)
    - Nemerov, Howard, 1966-1990 (Box 15)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, 1994-1998, 2007 (Box 15)
    - Nielsen, Bonnie, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Noel, Dan, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Noel, Susan K., 1977-2004, undated (Box 15)
    - Nolan, Pat, 1976, undated (Box 15)
    - Norbu, Tshering, 1974-1979 (Box 15)
    - Norris, Kathleen (Academy of American Poets), 1971 (Box 15)
    - Norse, Harold, 1979-1994 (Box 15)
    - North, Charles, 1978-1988, 2000, 2002, 2005-2007, undated (Box 15)
    - Notley, Alice
      - Correspondence(2 folders), 1971-2004, undated (Box 15)
      - Manuscripts, 1975-1983, undated (Box 15)
    - Ochester, Ed, undated (Box 15)
    - O'Connor, Michael Patrick, 1970-2002 (Box 15)
    - Odell, Jay, 1972 (Box 15)
    - O'Gallagher, Liam, 1969-1973 (Box 15)
    - O'Hara, Frank, 1960, undated (Box 15)
    - O'Hare, Lynn, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Ohnemus, Gunter, 1991 (Box 15)
    - O-Lan(?), 1972, undated (Box 15)
    - Oldenburg, Patty, undated (Box 15)
    - Oliver, Akilah, 1993, 2001, 2005-2006 (Box 15)
    - Oliver, Doug
      - Correspondence, 1978-1994, 2000, undated (Box 15)
      - Printed material and miscellaneous, 1984, undated (Box 15)
    - Olmstead, Marc, 1976, 1997 (Box 15)
    - Olson, Kirby, 1980, undated (Box 15)
    - Olthuis, Norbert, 1962-1969, undated (Box 15)
    - O'Neil, Hank, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Orlovsky, Peter, 1971-1977 (Box 15)
    - Osborne, John, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
    - Osman, Jena, 1993-2003 (Box 15)
    - Ostriker, Alicia, undated (Box 15)
    - Oughton, John, 1973-1978 (Box 15)
    - Owen, Maureen, 1975-1991, 2000, undated (Box 15)
    - Owens, Rochelle, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Pacheco, Joe (Box 15)
    - Padgett, Ron
      - Correspondence (7 folders), 1969-2004, undated (Box 15)
      - Manuscripts
        - "Moveable Basketballs," undated (Box 15)
        - Editorial notes on Allen Ginsberg introduction to William Burroughs' Letters to Allen Ginsberg, 1981 (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous poetry manuscripts (2 folders), 1967-1972 (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous prose manuscripts, undated (Box 16)
      - Printed material, 1967-1972, undated (Box 16)
      - Photographs and artwork, undated (Box 16)
      - Notes and jottings, undated (Box 16)
      - Full Court Press
        - Correspondence, 1973-1983, undated (Box 16)
        - Legal documents and miscellaneous, 1973-1983, undated (Box 16)
    - Parmalee, Dorothy, 1992-1995, 2002 (Box 16)
    - Paschen, Elise, 1988-1993 (Box 16)
    - Pasqui, Graziana Rossi, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Patchen, Miriam, 1972-1997 (Box 16)
    - Patterson, Bobo, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Paverd, Laurence, 1997, 2001, undated (Box 16)
    - Pearlman, Bill, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Pelton, Helen, 1986-1989, undated (Box 16)
    - Pennington, Tim, 1975, undated (Box 16)
    - Perlmutter, Sheryl (University of North Carolina), 1981 (Box 16)
    - Perloff, Marjorie, 1975-1976, 2001 (Box 16)
    - Perreault, John, 1972-1974, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Perry, Charles ( Rolling Stone), undated (Box 16)
    - Peters, Nancy
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1971-1997, 2000, 2007, undated (Box 16)
      - City Lights Books royalty statements and miscellaneous, 1978-1994, undated (Box 16)
    - Pettet, Simon, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Peyes, Craig, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Peyrafitte, Nicole, 1997-2002, undated (Box 16)
    - Phillips, Bryan, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Phillips, William ( Partisan Review), 1974-1981 (Box 16)
    - Phipps, Wanda, 1993-1997 (Box 16)
    - Pickard, Tom, 1975-1983, undated (Box 16)
    - Pietsch, Michael (Harmony Books), 1988 (Box 16)
    - Ping, Wang
      - Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 16)
      - Manuscript, Of Flesh and Spirit, undated (Box 16)
    - Piper, Adrian, 1969 (Box 16)
    - Pivano, Fernanda, 1977-1980 (Box 16)
    - Plymell, Charles, 1971-1975, 1986, undated (Box 16)
    - Pollet, Sylvester, 1996-1998 (Box 16)
    - Pomeroy, Joe, undated (Box 16)
    - Pommy-Vega, Janine, 1974-1981, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Porter, Anne, 1975 (Box 16)
    - Posset, Benn, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Post, Jon, 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - Pozzi, Giantonio, 1979, 2001, undated (Box 16)
    - Presson, Bill, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Prevallet, Kristen, 1993-2003, undated (Box 16)
    - Price, Laurie, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Pritchard, Norman Henry, 1973 (Box 16)
    - Pritchett, Patrick, 1997-2003 (Box 16)
    - Pritikin, Renny, 1985 (Box 16)
    - Puttmann, Christian, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Quasha, George, 1974-1975, 1999-2001 (Box 16)
    - Quinlan, Jim (Creative Music Studio), 1978 (Box 16)
    - Quirk, Mindy, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Quist, Susan, 1975 (Box 16)
    - Rachlis, Eugene (Bobbs-Merrill Company), 1974 (Box 16)
    - Raines, Bob, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Rakosi, Carl, 1979-1992 (Box 16)
    - Ramke, Bin ( Denver Quarterly), 1992 (Box 16)
    - Ramstedt, Martin, 1990-2001, 2006 (Box 16)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1978 (Box 16)
    - Randell, Elaine, 1976 (Box 16)
    - Randolph, Leonard (National Endowment for the Arts), 1973-1974. undated (Box 16)
    - Ratcliff, Carter, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Ravage, Alan (Bantam Books), 1971 (Box 16)
    - Rawlings, Carol, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Raworth, Tom, 1971-1978, 2002, undated (Box 16)
    - Reed, Ishmael, 1975, undated (Box 16)
    - Reed, Kim, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
    - Reed, Lou, 1978, undated (Box 16)
    - Reker, Mary Lou, undated (Box 16)
    - Renwick, Vanessa, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Reynolds, John, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Rezek, John, ( OUI magazine), 1974 (Box 16)
    - Reznikoff, Charles, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Ricard, Rene, 1976, undated (Box 16)
    - Richards, Brian (Bloody Twin Press), 1987-1988 (Box 16)
    - Richey, Joe
      - Correspondence (2 folders), 1982-2002, undated (Box 16)
      - Manuscripts, 1994-1997, undated (Box 16)
    - Riley, Denise, 1980-1984, undated (Box 17)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Roark, Randy, 1982-2003, undated (Box 17)
    - Roberts, Frances, 1978 (Box 17)
    - Robertson, Michael, 1974 (Box 17)
    - Robinson, Peter (Cambridge Poetry Festival), 1979 (Box 17)
    - Rockwell, Martha
      - Correspondence (5 folders), 1965-1979, undated, 5.0 folders (Box 17)
      - Manuscripts, undated (Box 17)
      - Artwork, undated (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 17)
    - Rodefer, Stephen, 1973-1986, undated (Box 17)
    - Rodney, Janet, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Rome, David, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Rooney, J.K., 1964, undated (Box 17)
    - Rosenberg, David, 1978, undated (Box 17)
    - Rosenberg, Mike, undated (Box 17)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1974 (Box 17)
    - Rosenthal, Bob
      - Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 17)
      - Manuscript "India Journal," 1985 (Box 17)
    - Rosenthal, M.L., 1975 (Box 17)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome
      - Correspondence, 1973-2002, undated (Box 17)
      - Manuscripts, 1976, undated (Box 17)
      - Printed, 1970-1994 (Box 17)
      - Interview, 1976, 1995, undated (Box 17)
      - Syllabus, undated (Box 17)
    - Rowan, Peter, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Rubin, Deborah, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Ruggia, James, 1986, undated (Box 17)
    - Rumaker, Michael, 1983 (Box 17)
    - Ruppert, Jim, undated (Box 17)
    - Russakoff, Molly, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Ruuttila, Eero (?), 1976 (Box 17)
    - Ryan, Bill (KCSU, Fort Collins), 1979 (Box 17)
    - Sabina, Maria, undated (Box 17)
    - Sakaki, Nanao, 1979-1991, 1999, undated (Box 17)
    - Sander, Ellen, 1974 (Box 17)
    - Sanders, Ed
      - Correspondence, 1973-2001, undated (Box 17)
      - Manuscripts
        - "The Gobble Gang Poems," 1962-1964 (Box 17)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 17)
    - Sandy, Stephen, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Santoli, Al, 1976 (Box 17)
    - Santos, Cristian, 1990, undated (Box 17)
    - Saroyan, Aram, 1967, 1986, 2001, undated (Box 17)
    - Savage, Tom, 1976-2003 (Box 17)
    - Sawyer-Laucanno, Christopher, 1991 (Box 17)
    - Scalapino, Leslie
      - Correspondence, 1985-2004 (Box 17)
      - Manuscript, "New Time," 1995 (Box 17)
    - Schaff, David, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Schecter, Danny, 1980 (Box 17)
    - Schelling, Andrew